{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "A friend is going to the market. You need some fruit, so you ask him: 'Do you think you ___ get me a kilo of oranges and some bananas, please?'",
            "a": "can",
            "b": "could",
            "c": "may",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "A: What shall I wear for Anna's party?\nB: You _________ wear your green dress, or the blue one. They're both nice.\nA: OK. I'll try them on.",
            "a": "could have worn",
            "b": "must wear",
            "c": "could wear",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why didn't you tell me that you wanted a sandwich? I ___ one for you when I made mine.",
            "a": "can't have made",
            "b": "could have made",
            "c": "could make",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Amy ___ in her diary to see if she could go to the cinema with Jack on Tuesday. She already knew that she wasn't free then.",
            "a": "didn't need to look",
            "b": "needn't look",
            "c": "mustn't look",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ___ be late for the train. I don't want to miss it.",
            "a": "needn't",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "don't have to",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "No one knew Sam's birthday was last week. He ___ anyone.",
            "a": "must have told",
            "b": "needn't have told",
            "c": "can't have told",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can hear the television in Joe's room. He ___ the athletics on the satellite channel. I know he wanted to watch them.",
            "a": "must be watching",
            "b": "can't be watching",
            "c": "mustn't be watching",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " When my father was young, he ________ work in the garden for long hours.",
            "a": "can ",
            "b": "could ",
            "c": "will ",
            "d": "should",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " He ________ have committed the crime because he was with me that day.",
            "a": "mustn't ",
            "b": "shouldn't     ",
            "c": "won't ",
            "d": "couldn't",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " Since we have to be there by 30, we ________ take a taxi.",
            "a": "had better       ",
            "b": "may ",
            "c": "ought ",
            "d": "are able to",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "27",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}